weshop.com 2011-06-25

# WeShop - The Consumer Network

**Privacy Statement**

Effective 02/10/2011

WeShop, Inc.  
32 E 31st Street  
12th Floor  
New York, NY 10016  
Phone: 1-(888)-weshop1

**Privacy**

We NEVER reveal any personally identifiable information about you. Your information is just that – yours! WeShop keeps your information completely secure. We don't reveal it to anyone without your permission. 

This privacy statement describes how WeShop collects and uses the personal information you provide on our Web site: [http://www.weshop.com](http://www.weshop.com/). It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.

WeShop has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at [info@weshop.com](mailto:info@weshop.com) or you can contact [TRUSTe here](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint). The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this Web site, and does not cover information that may be collected through software downloaded from the site.

**Transparency**

Whatever shopping data WeShop collects from you, you'll see. Anytime WeShop collects shopping data from you, you'll see it when you log in to your account. Shopping-based data is the only data WeShop's systems collect from a connected email address. That's it.

**Authority**

WeShop gives you the tools to take control of your purchasing information, and benefit from it! Details about the things you buy – clothes, food, music, tickets – are valuable to merchants and marketers to make you offers. WeShop believes this information is YOURS and yours alone. You should control it and how it is used. Access to your information should be on your terms and you should benefit by getting great offers in return for the things you want at the prices you want to pay. In addition, you should be able to share information about your purchases with other consumers, so you can find out where they bought the things you want and what they paid for them. In this way consumers can learn from each other where the great deals are, and what products and services are in demand, without constantly being pitched by merchants.

**Our Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy describes the manner in which WeShop, Inc., which operates the www.weshop.com site, uses and protects the information which you either send us as a result of ads, promotions, or communications, or which you allow us to learn as a result of your use of the WeShop site. We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes in our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the changes becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

Our aim is to adhere to the highest standards of online privacy, and to safeguard your information at all times. **We will never share any personally identifiable information about you with any person without your consent.**

By using the WeShop Sites you are agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Policy, and also to our Terms of Use. Please note that this Privacy Policy does not cover the use and collection of information on any non WeShop Site, including any site linked to or accessible through any of the WeShop Sites.

We collect information from you in three ways: (1) When you register with WeShop you provide us with your e mail address and password. Following registration, you then send us, or we acquire with your permission through certain technological interventions, various details on your shopping and purchasing transactions. If you choose to purchase a product from the site we will collect information such as name, address, and credit card information.; (2) When you visit the WeShop Sites, we automatically collect information such as your IP address, domain name, the type of browser you used, which site you came to us from, how long you spent on our site, and what pages you viewed; and (3) When you contact us directly, we collect any information you chose to share with us as part of such communication. 

We strive to give you as much control as possible over the way information is collected and used: (1) We use cookies which reside on your computer's hard drive to recognize automatically when you visit the WeShop Sites, and make your experience faster and more productive. You can set your browser not to accept such cookies, or you can delete the cookies that from time to time reside on your hard drive. However, deleting our cookies may substantially restrict the manner in which you can view or use the WeShop Sites, and your use of any WeShop services; and (2) Similarly, some of our advertisers, marketing partners and consultants (Òthird partiesÓ) may also use cookies for similar purposes which you may obtain from any of the WeShop Sites. We do not control or receive any information from such third party cookies, but we do record when you respond to third party messages carried on the WeShop Sites, and in certain cases through Òweb beaconÓ technology also record any further action (e.g. such as making a purchase) you take as a result of such third party messages. We also may use web beacon technology to inform us when you open an email communication from us. 

**Links to Other Web Sites**

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of WeShop, Inc. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Web site you visit.

**Agents/Service Providers**

We will provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as billing and shipping. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

**Testimonials**

In the event you compliment our services in a communication to us, we might use this testimonial on our site by quoting your compliment and attributing the testimonial to you (first name only plus the initial capital letter of your last name). You may request to have your testimonial removed by contacting us at [support@weshop.com](mailto:support@weshop.com).

**Security**

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at [support@weshop.com](mailto:support@weshop.com).

**Accessing and Correcting Person**

Please note that users cannot update or delete previously submitted information. If your email address should change, we ask that you contact us at [support@weshop.com](mailto:support@weshop.com) to change the email address associated with your account.

**Choice/Opt-Out**

When you choose to create an account with us we will send you a daily email offer which you may view or log into your account and cash in for coins. You may choose to stop receiving your daily email offer, newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in the emails you receive.

Data Retention:

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at [support@weshop.com](mailto:support@weshop.com). We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**Tell-A-Friend**

If you choose to use our referral service to refer a friend, send to a friend, email a page, or invite a friend to our site, we will ask you for your friend's email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. WeShop stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program.

**Facebook Connect**

You can log in to our site using Facebook Connect. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network.

**Legal Disclaimer**

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

**Business Transactions**

In the event WeShop, Inc. goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.

**Contacting Us**

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [support@weshop.com](mailto:support@weshop.com) or call 1-888-WeShop1 (888-937-4671).

WeShop, Inc.  
32 East 31st Street  
12th Floor  
New York, NY 10016
